betbright.com 2016-04-22

# Resource Centre - BetBright

**Our Safety is your Security**  
Dedsert is committed to protecting your privacy. Our Privacy Policy is to ensure that you can comfortably and safely use the service safe in the knowledge that your information and communications are secure, private and confidential. We greatly respect the privacy of our users and have developed this policy to demonstrate our commitment to protecting your privacy. Information that we collect about you is only ever used to deliver the service to you both efficiently and to the best of our ability. 

**General**  
This Privacy Policy is intended to describe for you, as an individual who is a user of the website and or the service, the information we collect, how that information may be used and with whom it may be shared. 

This is a legal document which outlines how the Company handles any data which may be associated with or identifies you in any manner. We encourage you to read it in conjunction with our [Terms & Conditions](https://www.betbright.com/content/terms) of which this Privacy Policy forms a part. It is also your responsibility to review this Privacy Policy frequently as we may modify it at our discretion in your best interests and or under instruction from any relevant body pertaining to the retention of private data. Every time you visit the website or use the Service and provide us with information, by doing so you are accepting the policies and practices described in this Privacy Policy at that time. If you have any questions about our Privacy Policy or how your data is stored or used, please do not hesitate to contact us directly by emailing [support@betbright.com](mailto:support@betbright.com). 

**What personal information do we collect, how do we use it and how is it kept secure?**  
We may collect personal information that identifies you such as your name, mobile phone number and email address and may also collect information that does not identify you. 

We may collect and store any personal information you enter on our website or provide to us in some other manner. This includes identifying information, such as your name, address, email address, and telephone number, and, if you transact business with us, financial information such as your payment method (valid credit card number, type, expiration date or other financial information). We also may request information about your interests and activities, your gender and age, and other demographic information such as your hometown, your gender or your username. 

**How we use your information.**  
The information we collect may be used to deliver the service to you efficiently and to the best of our ability. With this information we can manage your profile, select and serve relevant adverts to you and others, support your requests and needs, analyse your use of or interest in our services and or alternative services, content or products, and of those offered by others through our website and service. We can liaise and communicate with you by email, post, telephony devices and other available communication mediums about services that we deem to be of interest to you either from us or our partners. 

**Examples of how we may use your personal information and data;**

  1. Processing your bets, including card and online payments.
  2. Setting up, operating and managing your account.
  3. Complying with legal and regulatory requirements.
  4. Creating and building up personal profiles.
  5. Carrying out customer research, surveys and analysis.
  6. Providing you with information about specials, promotional offers and our products and services.
  7. Monitoring transactions for the purposes of preventing fraud, irregular betting, money laundering and cheating.

For advertising and promotional purposes, we may publish players' initials and/or geographic location (e.g. London), along with any winnings and prizes received, on the websites. 

**Other people's information.**  
We may also collect and store personal information about other people that are provided to us by you. For example, if you use our website or the service to inform or introduce others to the service, e.g. a referral, we may store their information that has been provided by you in order to inform them of the service or provide them with the information requested by you and to facilitate future activities. 

**Customer Support**  
Contact, including telephone calls to and from our Customer Support team may be recorded for training and security purposes along with the resolution of any queries arising from the service you receive. 

**IP Address & Cookies.**  
We automatically collect your IP address and record the web page from which you originated if you are using the service's website. Cookies are used to increase your security, not infringe on your privacy. In order to monitor, facilitate, administer and optimise the website and service for users and to earmark any possible technical issues that may arise within the website or the service, we may use your IP address to help identify you, tend to any difficulties and to gather demographic and profile information. We also use the 'cookies' to collect information about your online activity on our website, such as the web pages you visit, the links you click, and the searches you conduct on our website. Most browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can modify your web browser setting to decline cookies. If you choose to do this you may not be able to avail of some or all of the functionalities that the website or the service may offer. 

**Information that is collected by third parties.**  
We may allow third parties to advertise on our website or in the service. These companies may also use conventional tracking technologies in order to collect information about users or members who view or interact with their advertisements. This information allows them to target their advertising and gauge their effectiveness. Some of these third parties may offer a single location to opt out of advertising. You understand that information that other websites collect from you on our website or in our service, regardless of whether or not they carry our identity or other references to us, is not controlled by us, nor is their businesses. This Privacy Policy does not apply to these websites unless clearly stated. We encourage you to read their individual privacy policies. 

**Disclosure of Information**  
We may share your information with selected third parties including: 

  1. Business partners, suppliers and sub-contractors for the performance of contracts which we enter into with them or with you;
  2. Networks that require the data to select and serve relevant adverts to you and others (see ‘Third Party Tailored BetBright communication’ below);
  3. Analytics and search engine providers that assist us in the improvement and optimisation of the website; and
  4. Credit reference agencies for the purpose of assessing your credit score where this is a condition of us entering into a contract with you

We are entitled to share the information we hold on you which includes personal data and betting history with the regulator, sporting bodies and other bodies, including the police, in order to investigate fraud, money laundering or sports integrity issues and to comply with our regulatory duties to the UK Gambling Commission. We will retain information for a period of time (generally not more than six years) after closure of your account. All such information will be held in accordance with this Privacy Policy. 

**Third Party Tailored BetBright Communications**   
Third parties for which BetBright provide information for the purpose of serving you with BetBright communications tailored to your interest on their websites include Facebook and Twitter, whose privacy policies describe how your data is used at <https://twitter.com/settings/security> and <https://www.facebook.com/policy.php>. 

You can opt not to have your information used for BetBright communication purposes by Facebook and Twitter by following instructions on the following webpages: <https://www.facebook.com/about/ads> and <https://twitter.com/settings/security>. 

You may also tailor your BetBright contact preferences [here](https://www.betbright.com/account/profile). 

**Opting Out of Third Party Tailored BetBright Communication**   
To learn more about tailored communication and the ways you can manage third party tailored and mobile web communications, you may visit the following websites: 

  1. The Network Advertising Initiative ConsumerOpt-Out Page   
<http://www.networkadvertising.org/choices/>
  2. The Digital Advertising Alliance Opt-Out Page for U.S.-based advertising   
<http://www.aboutads.info/choices/>
  3. Your Online Choices UK website for EU-based advertising   
<http://www.youronlinechoices.com/uk/your-ad-choices>

These websites and tools are not provided by Dedsert. Dedsert does not control or operate these third party websites or tools and it is not responsible for the choices that advertisers provide through these tools. 

**Security of information.**  
We ensure that all personal information that you supply is securely stored by us in accordance with the requirements set out in the the Data Protection Acts 1988 and 2003 (the “DPA”). All personal information stored by us is stored in secure and controlled facilities with protected access to this information restricted to only persons who require access to the same information. 

All systems, procedures and policies are regularly maintained and assessed to ensure maximum security. If you apply for an account with us then to help us make credit decisions about you, to prevent fraud, to check your age and identity and to prevent money laundering, we may use third parties including credit reference agencies who will record any searches on your file. We may also make enquiries of, and disclose details of how you conduct your account to, such agencies, security organisations and any other relevant third parties for fraud and money laundering prevention. 

**Internet-based transfers**  
Given that the Internet is a global environment, using the Internet to collect and process personal data necessarily involves the transmission of data on an international basis. Some of the data processors engaged to process personal data may be based outside of the European Economic Area (EEA). Therefore, by browsing the Website and communicating electronically with us, you acknowledge and agree to our (or our suppliers or sub-contractors) processing your personal data outside the EEA. We will take all reasonable steps to ensure that your information and data is treated securely and in accordance with this Privacy Policy. 

**Access to information**  
You are entitled to access the information held about you. Your right of access can be exercised in accordance with the DPA. Any access request may be subject to a fee of £10 to meet our costs in providing you with details of the information we hold about you. 

**Changes to our Privacy Statement**  
Any changes we may make to our Privacy Policy in the future will be posted on this page and any such changes will become effective upon posting of the revised Privacy Policy. If we make any material or substantial changes to this Privacy Policy we will use reasonable endeavours to inform you by email, notice on the Website or other agreed communications channels. If you have any questions or queries regarding this Privacy Policy or any concerns regarding Data processed via the website, please contact us by emailing us at [support@betbright.com](mailto:support@betbright.com). 

© 2012 Dedsert 

Back to top
